

CONTACT



+4915771109914



wasemm@live.com



Github



Linkedin



Potsdam, 14480

Back end

Nodejs

Lowdb

Express

MongoDB

Mongoose

SKILLS

Front end

- HTML
- CSS
 - Sass
 - Bootstrap
- Javascript
 - React
 - DOM

Other

- Innovative
- Able to solve complex problems
- Service-focused

LANGUAGE

 Arabic **Native**

English

B2 German

WASEEM ALTINAWI

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Web developer with a strong interest in projects that require both conceptual and analytical thinking. Fully-committed to develop innovative applications that users will love. I have good communication skills and very good ability to adapt due to many years of experience in Customer Service and Sales .

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development

DCI Digital Career Institute gGmbH, Berlin (Remote) 2021 to 2022 Accomplishing a one-year-full-time training, covering Frontend and Backend Completing multiple practical projects to practice programming skills Taking German lessons as part of the course

Master's degree Anglophone Modernities in Literature and Culture

University of Potdam 2018 till now

• Bachelor's degree in English Literature

Damascus University 2005 to 2010

RELEVANT PROJECTS

Portfolio App

Personal portfolio website to showcase my skills and projects. The website includes a brief introduction and links to my social media profiles, a resume page, a projects page with a list of my projects and their descriptions, and a contact page with a contact form. The website is fully responsive and mobile-friendly, with a clean and modern design.

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Typed React, Sass, Tailwind, React Scroll, React Icons, Vercel

MERN+

Quiz App is a full-stack web application that allows users to take quizzes, solve code challenges, view results, and track progress. Utilizes MERN stack, and JavaScript, to create a dynamic and interactive platform. Demonstrates my abilities in front-end and back-end web development.

Technologies used: HTML, JavsScript, React, API, Tailwind, MongoDB, ExpressJs, JWT, Pssport, Google Auth, Judgeo, Monaco Editor, react-countdown-cirlce-timer, react pdf

Covid-19-Tracker

Creating App to track Covid-19 cases around the world spotting cases on the map and give daily and total deaths, recovers and cases statistics as well as the ability to search certain country

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, JavsScript, React, Api, Leafletjs-map ,Chart.js, Reactchartjs-2, Vercel

WORK EXPERIENCE

 Laravel Developer with API Integration internship eCommeleon 01/2023 02/2023

• Salesman at Kamps Bäckerei

2020 till now

Coordinator at Saudi Embassy (Switzerland) 2019 to 2020

Supervisor at "Fannat Company"

2010 to 2015